crossloop.com 2011-05-30

# CrossLoop - Privacy Policy

This CrossLoop privacy policy (the “ **Privacy Policy** ”) is intended to inform you of the policies and practices of CrossLoop, Inc. (“ **CrossLoop** ”, “ **us** ” or “ **we** ”) regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information.  Unless otherwise defined herein, certain capitalized terms shall have the meanings assigned to such terms in the Terms of Use available at http://www.crossloop.com/ipage.htm?id=termsofservice, which are hereby incorporated by reference.

**_Certain Definitions_**

**“Contact** **Information”** means information that allows someone to identify or contact you, including, for example, your name, address, telephone number, email address.

**“Personal Information”** is any information about you that is associated with or linked to your Account Information. 

**“Account Information”** means Personal Information that we collect during your registration for the CrossLoop Services and the creation of your Account profile, which may include your Contact Information, password for your account and password hint question, your screen name (“Screen Name”), your location, and email preferences. Account Information includes Personal Information we receive (if any) from any affiliate of, or entity related to, CrossLoop,  with which you have registered.  We may also ask you to provide additional information on an optional basis in connection with setting up your Account.  For example, once you have established an Account, you may provide additional information about yourself in the “Profile” section to describe your technical skills and professional experience, provide your location and language, and upload a photo of yourself, all of which will be deemed Account Information.  Providing this additional Account Information is optional, but it enables you to better identify yourself and market your technical support services to other users. ****

**“Anonymous Information”** means information that is not associated with or linked to your Contact Information; Anonymous Information does not permit the identification of individual persons. 

**_User Consent_**  
By using the CrossLoop Services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information according to this Privacy Policy.

**If you are a User who resides outside of the United States, you understand that your Personal Information may be processed in countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing of Personal Information may be less stringent than the laws in your country.**

**_Personal Information You Provide to Us_**  
When you register to use the CrossLoop Services, we collect your Account Information.  When you leave us feedback, we will collect any information that is contained in your feedback.   When you contact us by sending us an e-mail, fax, or letter, we will collect your address, fax number, or e-mail address and any information contained in the e-mail, fax, or letter you send us.  In addition, we collect transactional information based on your activities on the CrossLoop Services such as providing and receiving technical support and content you generate or that relates to your Account.   For example, we collect the feedback and ratings you provide after using the CrossLoop Services, your stated role or purpose for use of the services, and the number of sessions in which you use the CrossLoop Services.  ****

Your Screen Name is displayed throughout the CrossLoop Services and is therefore available to the public. All of your activity through the CrossLoop Services is traceable to your Screen Name. Other people can see your ratings and associated comments, feedback, technical support expertise, and so on.  We may send notices to other community members regarding suspicious activity and policy violations on our sites and refer to Screen Names in such notices. Therefore, if you associate your name with your Screen Name, the people to whom you have revealed your name will be able to personally identify your activities in connection with the CrossLoop Service. 

**_Personal Information Collected via Technology_**  
As you use the CrossLoop Services, certain information may also be collected passively, including your Internet protocol address, browser type and language, screen resolution, and operating system. CrossLoop may also store a small text file called a “Cookie” on your computer to store your login information. CrossLoop may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). 

An “ **Internet protocol address** ” or “ **IP Address** ” is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet.  CrossLoop may track the IP addresses used for sessions and store this information for security reasons and for the purpose of identifying any misuse of the CrossLoop Services. ****

**_Use of Information_**  
We use your Personal Information to provide the CrossLoop Services to you, to respond to requests that you make, to improve the CrossLoop Services, and to better tailor the features, performance and support of the CrossLoop Services.  Without limiting the foregoing, certain of your Personal Information may be included in a CrossLoop Badge (”Badge”), which is a widget and an optional service we provide to help you publish your CrossLoop profile on other sites, blogs and social networks in order to promote yourself and your technical skills.  At your request, we will publish the Personal Information contained in your Badge and distribute the information to third party websites, including blogs and social profiles, and third parties will be able to contact you through a link on your Badge.

We may use your Personal Information to send you electronic newsletters or promotional e-mails, unless you have requested not to receive such promotional communications from us.  We may also use your Personal Information to send you communications related to the CrossLoop Services.  ****

We may create Anonymous Information records from Personal Information by excluding your Contact Information (which makes the information personally identifiable to you).  We reserve the right to use and disclose Anonymous Information to third parties in our discretion. 

**_Spam_**  
CrossLoop does not tolerate or advocate the sending of any unsolicited commercial emails or spam. You may not add any other user of the CrossLoop Services, even a user who has received technical support from you, to your mailing list (email or physical mail) without that user’s express consent. To report CrossLoop-related spam or spoof emails to CrossLoop, please forward the email to [customersupport@crossloop.com](mailto:customersupport@crossloop.com).  You may not use any communication tools provided through the CrossLoop Services to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate this Privacy Policy or the Agreement. 

**_Feedback_**  
If you provide feedback to us, we may use and disclose such feedback for any purpose, provided that, except as expressly contemplated in this Privacy Policy, we do not associate such feedback with your Contact Information.  Notwithstanding the foregoing, (a) if you provide session feedback about your use of the CrossLoop Services, we shall display such feedback on the Website together with your Screen Name and/or photograph, and (b) if another user provides feedback about his experience with you, we shall display that feedback together with your Screen Name and/or photograph.

**_Disclosure of Personal Information_**  
Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not trade, rent, or share your Personal Information with third parties, unless you ask or authorize us to do so. 

We may provide your Personal Information to third party service providers who work on behalf of or with us to provide the CrossLoop Services.  However, these service providers do not have any independent right to share this information (except pursuant to a legal requirement such as a subpoena or warrant). 

We may share some or all of your Personal Information with our Affiliates (“ **Affiliates** ” are parent companies, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control), in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.  ****

If our company or our assets related to this Privacy Policy are acquired by another company, that company may possess the Personal Information collected by us and in such case it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**_Law Enforcement Compliance_**

We may, and you hereby authorize us to, disclose your Personal Information if required by law, to any enforcement officers acting under the color of law, or if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on us; or (b) to protect or defend the rights, property, or safety of CrossLoop, you, other users, or third parties.

**_Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Information_**  
We offer you choices regarding the collection, use and sharing of your Personal Information. When you receive promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further promotional communications from us and you will have the opportunity to “opt-out” by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the promotional e-mail you receive or by contacting us directly (please see contact information below).  
Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you administrative e-mails regarding the  CrossLoop Services, including, for example, purchase confirmation, account creation confirmation, and notices of updates to our Agreement or Privacy Policy.    
You may review and/or change any of your Account Information by editing it in your Account page.  You may also change the settings for your Account by editing the information under the settings tab. You may request the termination of your Account and deletion of your Account Information by us, but please note that we may be required (by law or otherwise) to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request only after we have fulfilled such requirements).   You may make such termination requests by sending an email request to [customersupport@crossloop.com](mailto:customersupport@crossloop.com), provided that you should send your request using the email account that you have registered for your Account.  When CrossLoop deletes Account Information, it will be deleted from the active database but may remain in CrossLoop’s archives. ****

**_Regarding Children_**  
We do not intentionally gather Personal Information about Users who are under the age of 13.

**_Other Sites and Third Party Information_**  
Our provision of links to other websites or locations is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such other websites or location or its contents. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites.

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to others, whether they are users of the CrossLoop Services or other sites throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. CrossLoop does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. 

**_Contact Us_**  
Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us:  [customersupport@crossloop.com](mailto:customersupport@crossloop.com)

**_Privacy Policy Updates_**  
This Privacy Policy is subject to revision, and if we make any substantial changes in the way we use or disclose your Personal Information, we will post a notice on this page.  If you object to any such changes, you must cease using the CrossLoop Services. Continued use of the CrossLoop Services following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

This Policy was last updated in November 2007.

© 2006-2011 CrossLoop Inc. All Rights Reserved.
